

(813) 210 - 5528 Jusixo@gmail.com Tampa - St. Pete, FL Available to relocate

Profile

Junior Developer specializing in Back-End Development, experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Strong background in project management and customer relations and committed to learn and grow in all aspects.

Programming Skills

Ruby on Rails, Back-End Web Development, SQL, MVC, HTML, CSS, API consuming & building, agile web development, responsive design, basic Ruby, console applications, ActiveRecord, CRUD, Javascript basics, jQuery basics, Ajax, Full-Stack Development

Experience

JUNIOR DEVELOPER, THE IRON YARD, TAMPA, FL - 2017-PRESENT

While at The Iron Yard I designed and created web apps that served multiple purposes that ranged from a news aggregator, real estate listing site, auction site and a local social networking site.

DISTRIBUTION SPECIALIST, BROWN DISTRIBUTING COMPANY, TAMPA, FL - 2015-2017

Local craft beer distribution for the Tampa Bay area, was in charge of ensuring safe delivery of product to customers and offering advice on which new products they should receive.

STORE MANAGER, ALDO GROUP, NEW YORK, NY - 2011-2015

As Store Manager for Aldo my job entailed the hiring training and evaluation of employees, customer service, supervision over sales and quota completions and tracking inventory.

ASSISTANT MANAGER, PUBLIX, TAMPA, FL - 2008-2011

The main focus of my time at Publix was customer service and ensuring every one had an engaging friendly experience. Other requirements included merchandise tracking, creating work schedule, and associate evaluations.

Education

The Iron Yard, Tampa, FL – Back end Engineering, 2017 Cooper Union, New York, NY – Architecture and Design, 2007-2008 Penn Foster High School, Scranton, PA – High School Diploma, 2007

Projects

WANDERER - HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/JUSIXO/WANDERER - JUNE 2017

Wanderer is a social marketing app for outdoor events and festivals. Connecting people to a drones camera feed they can view the event and get photos from a new angle.

BIDTASTIC - HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/JUSIXO/BIDTASTIC-MINUS-ONE - MAY 2017

Bidtastic is a charitable auction app that I was project lead on. The app was built mobile first and has the ability to host multiple auctions at a time. People can bid through the app and stay up to date with everything happening when the events timer ended the winners would automatically be informed.

HOUSEHUNTER - HTTPS://JUSIXO-HOUSEHUNTER.HEROKUAPP.COM - APRIL 2017

HouseHunter is an app that I created that was meant to show off skills I learned like using multiple databases, uploading images to a database, using authorization for signing in, javascript for real time search results, and action mailers.

MIXTAPES - HTTPS://JUSIXO-MIXTAPE.HEROKUAPP.COM - SEPTEMBER 2017

Mixtapes is a personal project of mine I wanted to create a better experience with sharing playlists I've created with friends and give them the ability to do the same in return. Main focus of the app is the create a better visual standard than what Spotify currently offers while keeping major parts to just one page so users wont have to go far to find a playlist they want to hear.

FINDYRPET - HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/JUSIXO/FINDYRPET - DUE DECEMBER 2017

Find your pet is an app I am designing to help people locate any lost pets they see around their neighborhood. The app will use location with maps and a geotagging system along with photos and descriptions of the pets to create a engaging service to help people find their pets easily.

GITHUB: HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/JUSIXO

LINKEDIN: HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/JUSIXO

PORTFOLIO: HTTPS://JUSIXO.GITHUB.IO